欢迎来到万圣节蝙蝠制作教程 欢迎来到万圣节蝙蝠制作教程
首先请将蝙蝠模型导入为虚拟模特 为它添加一下纹理
首先我们要制作蝙蝠耳朵版片 您可以根据自己的操作习惯绘制出一个耳朵版片
您可以将截图导入为2D背景图片作为绘制版片的参考
此处我们将顶部俯瞰的剪影图保存下来导入为2D背景图片
新增一个面料作为翼膜的面料并修改其颜色
接着使用多边形工具参考翅膀骨骼绘制出翼膜版片
使用筷子键V以将直线调整为弧线使用筷子键V以将直线调整为弧线
使用筷子键V以将直线调整为弧线
完成所有的硬膜后在3D窗口中旋转移动它们并放到大致对应的位置上
在3D窗口中单击右键选择模拟属性将重力数值调整为0
空气阻力设置为100防止板片滑动或坠落
此时为了将硬膜固定在3D空间中使用固定针工具固定住板片的几个角
使用固定针工具固定住板片的几个角
When opening the model, move the fixed needle to adjust the position of the film until it is close to the bone.
Next, select all the film models and print them, and then move the fixed needle to adjust the position of the bone.
Reduce the粒子間距 from 20 to 5, and use the fixed needle set tool to double-click on the point on the side where the film model is connected to the bone.
This operation will add a fixed needle to this side, and then create a fixed needle on the side where all the other film models are connected to the bone.
Next, select the fixed needle and select all the fixed needles in the right-click menu.
Then, select all the fixed needles and fix them to the virtual model.
Freeze all the sheets.
Use the same method to move the sheet of film into the right position.
硬化板片
Add a fixing needle at the joint of the ear plate and the bone.
Adjust the composition of the internal line used for making details later to the curve line.
Select the internal line control function to create several internal lines.
Adjust the composition of the internal line control function to create several internal lines.
Select these built-in internal lines and align them to the outside of the board.
Adjust the position of the internal line according to the needs.
Delete unnecessary curve points.
If you do not have the fold-up curve, you can turn it on to get a better reference effect.
To see how it works, select the
We can use this to create theŠo cheg of the band of the ear.
Track are showed here.
Draw the path to the previous窿 point using the ascending mouse mouse mouseout.
We will use this part to create the shape of the bully's ear, and move it to the position of his face.
To increase the strength of the wind, the wind blowing effect is more obvious.
Change the wind blowing type to Spherical, so that the wind is not blowing from one angle, but from the wind control period to the four sides and eight directions.
When the right effect is simulated, the cold hole is opened.
Use the internal circle tool to draw the holes on the wings.
On the right of the drawn circle, select and turn it into a hole.
Copy and paste a hole, and adjust its size as needed.
Next, create a new fabric, and create its shape based on the film.
Here you are!
Differesso
The
.
left
the right
the left
After the creation of these parts, use a sewing machine to sew them together.
You can also use a sewing machine to sew these parts together, but it is better to use a sewing machine to sew them together.
In the 3D window, put them in the right place, and then print these panels.
In order to make the fabric not wrinkled, we replaced it with leather fabric.
Now we return the fabric in the broken position to default for simulation, i.e. default fabric.
Then change all the broken parts and the lines of the one-piece seam to Turned, to make the seam position even.
So you can wind
Through simulation.
You will see the following.
Then, remove the hardening of all panels and deflate them.
Use symmetrical panels, panels and mortises to create a symmetrical panel on the other side.
Place these panels in the appropriate square area for the arrangement of UV.
Go to the UV editor, right-click in the background, and select the UV to be placed in the 2D arrangement position.
Right-click in the background again, select all UVs to be placed in the 0.1 position.
Insert the virtual model to the appropriate position.
Since the virtual model is placed in the 2D arrangement position,
we need to re-select the pins.
In the menu, right-click and select all pins to be placed on the virtual model.
Open the animation recording.
After recording, select all the inner lines on the ear.
Set the fold strength to 20, and the angle of fold to 220.
This will make the effect of each ear part more obvious.
Press the Fn key to close the
Dot model, and then press the Fn key to close the wire hole.
Select the hole.
Press the Fn key to close the hole.
and select the horizontal line on the left side.
Pour out the file and render it in the software you like
Marvelous Designer can also successfully complete the
animation of this wing model
Then, create a fixed frame along the outline of the film
and attach these fixed frames to the virtual model
Record animation
This method
is also suitable for wings with very bright shapes
such as the wings of dragons
This method is best suited for fans of fighting members
The Closed Captions work only if you like this video.
Thank you